https://www.donationline.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy – Donation Line
DonationlineQuestions & AnswersCharity SearchDonate Now!Tax infoBlog Call 1-877-227-7487
VEHICLE DONATION CENTERMake a car donation today & help a charity of your choice Donate nowprivacy policyDonation Line, LLC respects the privacy of all its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains our treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on DonationLine.com. Last Update: January, 20091. Data Collection DonationLine.com will not collect or use any personally identifying information about the visitors to the website; your visit to the web site is anonymous.This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.2. Cookies To enhance your experience with our site, some of our web pages use “cookies”. Cookies are small text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, by registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.3. Links to Other Sites DonationLine.com may contain links to other websites. DonationLine.com does not monitor or control the content of other web sites or whether such websites collect or process your personal data. Accordingly, DonationLine.com assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review the separate privacy policies of such sites.4. Information Sharing DonationLine.com does not sell, rent or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, name, email address, mailing address, to other companies or individuals.Information you provide on the Donation Form will be provided to our affiliates and the charitable organization(s) for the purposes of processing your donation only.5. Changes to This Policy DonationLine.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted here on the site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy.6. Contact Information For questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us.Contact Information: DonationLine, LLC. Toll-free phone: 1-888-448-3345 Fax: (860) 228-9037 E-Mail: donate@donationline.com
DONATE YOUR VEHICLE NOW
no cost, no hassle, absolutely FREE vehicle donation processSelect a CharitySelect a Charity1 Step Further Community Center1touch Project9th Life HawaiiA Place For TeensA Safe PlaceA Simple House of Sts. Francis and AlphonsusAberg Center for LiteracyAblechildAbundant Life Restoration Ministries Inc.Academy for Learning and Character DevelopmentActs of Benevolence, CorpAdopt-A-Dog Inc.Adoption HealingAdvocates 4 Animals Feline Rescue & Rehabilitation IncAfrican Aid Organization, Inc.African American Cultural Center IncAfrican American Mutual Assistance Network Inc.African People's Education & Defense FundAgape Home, Inc.AIDS Project East BayAiredale Rescue Group of South CarolinaAlachua Conservation TrustAlie FoundationAll Border Collie RescueAll Dog Rescue, IncAll Dogs Official Rescue EnterpriseAll Star Pet Rescue IncAllergy & Asthma Network Mothers of AsthmaticsAlley's HouseAlliance
for Safe Kids, Inc.Alpine Valley SchoolAltamaha RiverkeeperAlzheimer's Association Connecticut ChapterAmerica for Veterans FoundationAmerican Brain Tumor AssociationAmerican Foundation for Suicide PreventionAmerican Library AssociationAmerican River ConservancyAMVETS POST 911 NJAngel of Hope Animal RescueAnimal Alliance of Cape May County Inc.Animal Care and Control TeamAnimal PlaceAnimal Rescue KonnectionAnimal Rescue Rhode IslandAnimal Shelter of Northeast NebraskaAnimal Welfare AssociationAnimal Welfare League of Frederick County IncAnimal Welfare Society, Inc.Antiochian Orthodox Christion Archdiocese, Depart of Youth MinistryApache Junction Horse RescueAquAllianceAquinas AcademyArrowhead Neuroscience Foundation, Inc.AS220Asian Elephant SupportAsian Services in Action, Inc.Asperger/Autism Network, Inc.Assistance League of Temecula ValleyAssisted Living Center, Inc.Atlantic City BalletAudio Information Network of ColoradoAutism Services and Resources ConnecticutBaltimore Animal Rescue & Care ShelterBasicNecessities Inc.Basset Buddies Rescue of TexasBattenkill ConservancyBayou Meets The Bay Classic FoundationBello Machre, IncBerlin-Peck Memorial LibraryBig Brothers Big Sisters of New HampshireBigUms Soup KitchenBillerica Cat Care CoalitionBlue Ridge Wildlife CenterBluePath Service DogsBoston Area Rape Crisis CenterBoston Jewish Music FestivalBoys & Girls Club of Greater WatervilleBoys & Girls Club of Lenoir CountyBoys & Girls Club of StamfordBoys & Girls Club of VinelandBrandywine Valley SPCABreaking the CycleBreeder Release Adoption ServiceBrennan Center for JusticeBridges Domestic & Sexual Violence SupportBridges to HopeBridgeway Christian ChurchBroken Tail RescueBrown County Humane SocietyButte Environmental CouncilC.A.B. FoundationCaldwell Animal RescueCalRTA Educational FoundationCalvary Lutheran SchoolCancer Support Community of the Greater Lehigh ValleyCare 4 My Lambs, IncCaregiver Volunteers of Central New Jersey-A Faith, Action ProgramCaring For Creatures FoundationCarolina Basset Hound Rescue Inc.Carroll Hill Industries, Inc.Carroll Hospice, Inc.Carroll Hospital Center FoundationCASA of Harford CountyCasey Cares FoundationCat Adoption and Rescue Efforts, Inc.Cat Angel Network IncCat Coalition Inc.Catholic Schools of Broome CountyCATS Northeast, Inc.Catty Shack Ranch Wildlife SanctuaryCedar Springs Waldorf SchoolChabad Center of Natick Inc.Chesapeake Shakespeare CompanyChess and Community Conference, Inc.Chico Peace & Justice CenterChild Evangelism Fellowship of North Central IndianaChildren of the NationsChildren's Rescue Outreach InternationalChildrens Community SchoolChinese American Community ConnectionsChinese Children Adoption InternationalChinese Service Center USAChinmaya Mission ChicagoChocolate Chip Dalmatian Assistance LeagueChrist Church Episcopal, NeedhamChristian Fellowship Outreach Mission Inc.Christian Freedom InternationalChristian Outreach in ActionChristian People Pulling Together InternationalCITYstageClackamas River Basin CouncilCoalition for AnimalsColonial Baptist ChurchColorado Center for Hospice & Palliative CareCommunity Cats CoalitionCommunity Services for Children, Inc.Community Thrift of ManassasCommunity Youth ServicesCompass Montessori Education FoundationCompassionate Care ALSCongregation Agudas AchimConnecticut Audubon Society Center at FairfieldConnecticut Audubon Society Center at GlastonburyConnecticut Audubon Society Center at MilfordConnecticut Audubon Society Center at PomfretConnecticut Audubon Society EcoTravelConnecticut Audubon Society Greatest NeedsConnecticut Audubon Society RTPECCORD USA Inc.Courageous Women AssociationCozy Cat Cottage Adoption CenterCross-Lines Community Outreach, Inc.Cure HHTDanbury Animal Welfare SocietyDavis Waldorf SchoolDelaware Pro Life CoalitionDelmarva Cat Connection, Inc.Democracy North CarolinaDenver Children's Advocacy CenterDesert Ridge High Orchestra BoosterDIAL - Center for Independent LivingDisaster and Wilderness Ground SearchersDiscovery Eye FoundationDoberman Rescue of North TexasDogs Deserve BetterDogs for Better Lives (formerly Dogs for the Deaf)Dogs Without BordersEastern Iowa Miles for MyelomaECAN Esophageal Cancer Action Network, Inc.ElderPetElizabeth Baptist ChurchElsa's ArkFairfax4HorsesFaith Christian SchoolFaith in God Ministries Inc.Family & Children's Service, Inc of Monmouth CountyFamily Missions CompanyFeline Rescue AssociationFeminist Women's Health CenterFeralCare Inc./Nutmeg Spay/Neuter ClinicFerrets Unlimited Rescue ServicesFidos For Freedom, Inc.Finger Lakes SPCA, IncFIYAFlorida Veterans For Common Sense Fund, Inc.Foodnet Meals on WheelsForever Home Rescue New EnglandForgotten Felines Inc.Forgotten Feral Felines of FloridaFound in TranslationFoundation for Educating Children with Autism (FECA)Fox Chase Cancer CenterFranklin Stage CompanyFreedom Guide Dogs For the BlindFresh Start, Inc.Friends of Autistic People, Inc. - FAPFriends of Felines Inc.Friends of Sheba Medical CenterFriends of the Cumberland Trail State ParkFriends of the Jemez Springs Public LibraryFriends of the Kern County Animal Shelters FoundationFriends of the Lawrence LibraryFriends of The Two Rivers Senior CenterFriends of Tiverton LibraryFurrever Friends Rescue & Volunteers IncGeer FoundationGentle Touch Animal SanctuaryGeorgia AGAPE, Inc.Georgia Cancer Support Inc.Georgia Right to Life Educational Trust FundGeorgia Tribe of Eastern Cherokee, Inc.GHA Autism SupportsGirl Scouts of the Green and White MountainsGirls BuildGishrei Shalom Jewish CongregationGods Got YouGolden Treasures Golden Retriever Rescue, Inc.Good Counsel, Inc.Good Karma Dog RescueGood News Home for WomenGood Shepherd FoundationGreater Cleveland Youth for ChristGreen Beret FoundationGreen Valley ChurchGREY2K USA Education FundGroton Dunstable Education Foundation, IncGuide Dogs of America-CT, RI, Western MAGuiding Eyes for the BlindHabitat for CatsHappy VillageHarlem Dowling-West Side Ctr For Children & Family ServicesHarmony Charity Organization, Inc.Hawaii Health & Harm Reduction CenterHeal With Love FoundationHealing the ChildrenHeart of Hope Asian American Hospice CareHeightened Independence & Progress (hip)Helping Hands: Monkey Helpers for the DisabledHendrick Hudson Community Educational FoundationHenry and William Evans Home for ChildrenHepatitis B FoundationHigh Point Treatment Center Inc.Hindu Swayamsevak Sangh USA Inc.Home Awaits Animal RescueHomeless Animal Rescue TeamHomeward Pet Adoption CenterHomeward Trails Animal RescueHopeful Ways IncHorsesaversHouse of RestorationHouse of RuthHouston Furniture BankHumane Society of Central TexasHumane Society of Cherokee CountyHumane Society of McCormick CountyHumility Outreach Missionary Ministries Inc.India Development & Relief FundInfinite Wishes FoundationInsulin PumpersInterfaith Neighbors IncInterfaith Volunteer Care Givers of Greater New HavenInternational Match Safe AssociationIslamic Circle of North AmericaIzaak Walton League of AmericaJefferson County Library FoundationJeremiah's CrossingJireh Ministries Foundation, Inc.Jonnycake Center of WesterlyJoslin Diabetes CenterKadampa Meditation Center ArizonaKARE Crisis NurseryKatonah Village LibraryKaumakapili ChurchKC Retired Greyhounds As PetsKeep A Child AliveKID smARTKids Alive InternationalKingston Cooperative PreschoolKSQM FMLake County Council on AgingLake Grove Presbyterian ChurchLake Traverse Animal RezcueLas Amigas Incorporated National Benefit FundLechaim Charities, IncLifeLine Youth and Family ServicesLifeStreamLift Every Voice and Sing Gospel Festival & FairLighthouse Shelter Inc.Lucky Horse Equine RescueLupus Foundation of Southern New YorkMAB Community Services (Formerly MA Assoc for the Blind)Maceo H Jones FoundationMarcellus Free LibraryMARCH, Inc. of ManchesterMarillac St. Vincent Family ServicesMarine Science and Nautical Training Academy - MANTAMaryland Horse RescueMaryland Ravens, Inc.Masonic Angel Foundation, IncMass Community Health ServicesMatthew HouseMayan FamiliesMedical Missions FoundationMedicines for HumanityMemorial Assistance MinistriesMen Stopping ViolenceMercy Housing & Shelter CorpMesothelioma Research Foundation of AmericaMid-Atlantic Asthma FoundationMid-Atlantic German Shepherd RescueMid-Atlantic Great Dane Rescue LeagueMidway LivingMile High Youth CorpsMilestones Behavioral ServicesMillsburg Outreach InternationalMinistries of Aides InternationalMinorities in Broadcasting Training ProgramMonroe County Friends of AnimalsMontessori School of LouisvilleMorning Star ChurchMultiple Myeloma Research FoundationMultiple Sclerosis FoundationMultiple Sclerosis Quality of Life ProjectMusic Made in HeavenMusic NorthwestNAMI Central VirginiaNAMI SeattleNational Alliance on Mental Illness ConnecticutNew Beginnings Pet RescueNew Britain Youth TheaterNew Camaldoli HermitageNew Directions for People with DisabilitiesNew England Center for Homeless VeteransNew Fairfield Free Public LibraryNew Hampshire Art AssociationNew Hampshire Children's TrustNew Hampshire Coalition Against Domestic and Sexual ViolenceNew Hope For WomenNew Jersey American VeteransNew Life Children's Home, Inc.New Life K-9 RescueNew Life MinistriesNew Mexico Family NetworkNewington Student Assistance FundNext Door Solutions to Domestic ViolenceNicholas House, IncNoah's Ark Animal Sanctuary Inc.North Carolina Victim Assistance NetworkNorthaven Assisted LivingNorthwest Animal Rights NetworkNorthwest Battle BuddiesNorthwest Indiana Hindu Religious CenterNOVACO Inc.NuPath, Inc.Olympic Evangelical Free ChurchOpen Door Animal SanctuaryOperation HomefrontOpportunity WorksOpus Aima ObscuraeOrangutan Foundation InternationalOrder of AHEPA Chapter 286Oregon Coalition Against Domestic & Sexual ViolenceOregon Disaster Medical TeamOrphan World ReliefOrphans of the StormOswego County Humane SocietyOur Neighbors' TableOxford Second Presbyterian ChurchPalm Beach ZooPalo Alto Art Center FoundationPamoja Tujenge BuildtogetherPancreatic Cancer Action Network, Inc.Parkwood Christian PreschoolPartnerships Center for Adult Day CarePathways to CollegePAWS - ConnecticutPAWS for PeoplePBGV Health and Rescue FoundationPeace, Love & PawsPelizaeus-Merzbacher Disease FoundationPennsylvania SPCAPETS Inc. Adopt-A-PalPets LifelinePhilippine Center of Ventura CountyPima Community College FoundationPitzer CollegePlaya Lakes Joint VenturePresbyterian Church in WestfieldPrevent Child Abuse St. Joseph CountyPrimary Aldosteronism FoundationPrincess, Inc.Project Future, Inc.Project Have HopeProject RedirectPromises Animal RescueProvidence Public LibraryPuget Sound Christian ClinicPuget Sound WildcarePurrs & Whiskers, Inc.Quincy Crisis CenterRabbit HavenRebuilding Together of Central FloridaReliance HouseRescued Love, Inc.Rescuties Animal Rescue, IncRethinking SchoolsRevival Now AmericaRidgefield Library AssociationRio Vista CARERoom for JoyRuth Keeler Memorial LibrarySaint Barbara Greek Orthodox ChurchSaint Raphael ParishSan Antonio Youth LiteracySan Francisco CATS Academy, Inc.Sanctuary OneSandy Rollman Ovarian Cancer Foundation Inc.Schoharie River Center Inc.Scott County Humane SocietySEEDSSEMCOA Inc.Seton Catholic Central, Binghamton, NYSewa International USAShelton Land Conservation Trust, Inc.Shepard Meadows Therapeutic Riding Center Inc.Sickle Cell Disease Assoc of Amer-Uriel Owens ChapterSierra Foothill ConservancySierra Wildlife RescueSionfonds for HaitiSOAR InitiativeSociety for the Preservation of Roman Catholic HeritageSojourner Truth Multicultural Art MuseumSolving Kids' Cancer Inc.Sonoma Valley Mentoring AllianceSouthside Center for Violence PreventionSpecial BunnySpecial Parents Information NetworkSri Venkateswara Swami (Balaji) TempleSt Peter's OrphanageSt Philip HouseSt Vincent De Paul CenterSt. Augustine Humane SocietySt. Louis Area FoodbankStandUp For KidsStrays and Others, IncStudent Action with FarmworkersSuwannee PAWS, IncT.A.I.L.S. (The Alliance In Limiting Strays)Tabor Community ServicesTASK-9, Inc.Tender Care Animal RescueThe Alcove Center for Grieving Children and FamiliesThe American Street Cat, Inc.The Bee FoundationThe CA GroupThe Cat HouseThe Cathedral Basilica of St. Francis of AssisiThe Clay StudioThe Connecticut Rivers Council - BSAThe Creators Gift 137The Douglas CenterThe Dwelling Place, Inc.The Foundation for Peripheral NeuropathyThe JF Kapnek TrustThe Kohn FoundationThe Network/La RedThe Oasis Animal SanctuaryThe Real Word Ministries Inc.The Ruffian FoundationThe Ruffugees FoundationThe Scholarship Fund of Concord and CarlisleThe Sharing Community, Inc.The Sudden Arrhythmia Death Syndrome Foundation (SADS)The Village for Families and ChildrenThe Whitfield Historical FoundationThreshold Community ProgramTitle IX Girls Running ClubTraining Rescue Dogs Inc.Trans World RadioTri-Lakes CaresTrue PassionTurning Points NetworkUNH Therapeutic Riding ProgramUnited Astronomy Clubs of New JerseyUnited States Veterans InitiativeUniversity of Maryland School of Medicine FoundationValley Feeding Project LLCVeterans for Common SenseVeterans in Christ CorporationVeterans Lodging, Inc.Vizsla Rescue HavenVocal RevolutionWaccamaw Youth CenterWakeman Memorial Association, Inc.Waldorf School of Saratoga SpringsWallingford Community Senior CenterWashington Education & Squash AcademyWatertown Boys and Girls ClubWest Suburban Humane Society No Kill Animal ShelterWild For Life FoundationWild Horse FoundationWild West VetsWildbird RecoveryWildlife Veterinary CareWomen Empowering Women, Inc. (WOW)WomenSafe IncWorld Population BalanceWycliffe Bible TranslatorsYosemite ConservancyYoung Life - Sedona & Verde ValleyYouth Catalytics, Inc.Youth Center Inc.Zebs Wish Equine SanctuaryOwner Name*Email* Street Address*City*State**StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces PacificZipcode*Is the vehicle at the same addressYesNoSreet AddressCityStateStateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces PacificZipcodeContact NamePhone*Alternate PhoneDonationDonation InformationCar, Truck or VanBoat or JetskiMotorcycleSnowmobileMotorhomeBoat YearVehicle YearBoat MakeVehicle MakeBoat ModelVehicle ModelBoat ColorBoat ColorBeigeBlackBlueBrownBurgundyCharcoalGoldGreyGreenOffwhiteOrangePinkPurpleRedSilverTanTurquoiseWhiteYellowVehicle ColorVehicle ColorBeigeBlackBlueBrownBurgundyCharcoalGoldGreyGreenOffwhiteOrangePinkPurpleRedSilverTanTurquoiseWhiteYellowBoat SizeEngine SizeBoat TypeBoat Identification NumberVehicle Identification NumberMileageNumber Of DoorsDo you have the title for this vehicle?YesNoDo you have the title for this Boat/Jetski?YesNoIs the trailer included with the Boat/Jetski?YesNoWe only accept boats on trailersTrailer Identification Number (VIN)Do you have the title for the trailer?YesNoDoes the vehicle run?YesNoVehicle Condition (i.e. any damages)Boat Condition (i.e. any damages)EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Donate Used Vehicle By StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWashington D.C.West VirginiaWisconsinWyomingDonate Used Vehicle By Vehicle MakeAcuraAlfa RomeoAMCAudiBMWBuickCadillacChevroletChryslerDaewooDaihatsuDatsunDodgeEagleFiatFordGeoGMCHondaHyundaiInfinitiInternationalIsuzuJaguarJeepKIALand RoverLexusLincolnMazdaMercedes BenzMercuryMGMitsubishiNashNissanOldsmobileOpelPeugeotPlymouthPontiacPorscheSaabSaturnScionSterlingStudebakerSubaruSuzukiToyotaTriumphVolkswagenVolvoDonationlineCharity SearchDonate Your CarFAQTax InfoRequest a QuoteDonate Used CarsDonate VehiclesDonate Junk CarAutomobile ResourcesAutomobile sitesDonate BoatDonate by StateDonate JetskisDonate MotorcycleDonate MotorhomeTax LawsSell Your Car NowShare:
Contact Email Call 1-877-227-7487 Fax 1-860-530-1682 Privacy Policy SitemapAll trademarks and registered trademarks appearing on
donationline.com are the property of their respective owners.Copyright © 2001-2017 DonationLine.com LLC.
